If this continues,
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)このままでは
必ず 第２第３の包帯悪魔が現れ➡
there will be more rag demons in our future
rising up to oppose mankind.
人間に牙をむくでしょう｡
You're so cute, Mugaro!
(ﾆｰﾅ･ﾄﾞﾗﾝｺﾞ)
ムガロちゃん かわいいです～！
あいつ 早く戻ってくるといいね｡
I hope he comes back soon.
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)
昼に 例の子供の力が発動された｡
The child unleashed his power
this afternoon.
Would you have been this much of
a pathetic crybaby ten years ago?
(ﾘﾀ)１０年前のあんたは
そんなに ウジウジ ウジウジ➡
ウダウダしてたかしらね｡
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)必ず➡
There has to be a path where
all three races can live in peace!
三種族が共に生きる道が
あるはずです｡➡
私は それを諦めない！
And I will never give up on it!
(ｼｬﾘｵｽ17世)お前は
お前の思うように生きてみよ｡
You live your life your way.
I will be doing what I feel is right.
私は 私の正義を貫くだけだ｡
変態！
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)うわぁ～～！
Pervert!
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)はい｡
Here.
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)ニ… ニーナちゃん
これでいいかな？
Nina, is this okay?
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ？
ニーナちゃ～ん？
Nina?
しつこい 変態｡
えっ あぁ…｡
Stop bothering me, pervert.
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ…｡
お嬢さん 思い出してください➡
Young lady...
Please remember how Bacchus
kindly opened up his home
行き場のなクワァったあなたに
住居を提供してくれた➡
to provide you a place to stay
when you had nowhere else to turn.
あのバッカスの優しさを｡
知らない｡
クワッ！
Whatever.
I think that's a bit cruel to dismiss.
｢知らない｣は
クワァわいそうでしょう｡
(ﾘﾀ)ニーナ
唐辛子と手羽先が足らないの｡➡
Nina, we don't have enough chili peppers
and chicken wings.
買ってきてくれない？
は～い｡
Could you go buy some?
Okay.
(ﾊﾝｻ)今年も
この手羽先料理ですクワァ？➡
You're making chicken wings again
this year? They were a big hit last year.
去年は 大繁盛でしたねぇ｡
(ﾘﾀ)
もっと買っておけばよかったわ｡➡
I should've bought more.
Nina will be in quite the predicament
if that handsome man
うわさのイケメンが食べに来て
売り切れだったら➡
shows up and we're out of wings.
ニーナが困るしね｡
えっ！
(ﾊﾝｻ)そうですねぇ｡ あの
腕相撲をしたイケメンが来たら➡
Yes, you're right. If that handsome man
you arm wrestled shows up,
ぜひ 食べさせたいですね｡
ちょっと やめてよ！
we've got to let him try some.
Hey, cut that out!
誰だ その男！ 俺は知らねぇぞ！
んんっ！
What's this man you're talking about?
Nobody told me about him!
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)あっ あっ…｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)あれは いい男でしたねぇ｡➡
He sure was a handsome man.
ノーブルで 威厳がありましたよ｡
He had a noble dignity about him.
(ﾘﾀ)来てくれるといいわねぇ｡
いってきま～す｡
-I hope he comes.
-I'm off, then!
あぁ～あ…｡
Did you know, Rita?
(ﾊﾝｻ)知ってます？ リタさん｡➡
Nina still keeps the ring that the man
left behind that day in her pocket.
お嬢さんは あの日
例の男が置いていった指輪を➡
いつまでも大事に
ポケットに入れてるんですよ｡
(ﾘﾀ)あらあら 随分 乙女チックね｡
My, how girly of her.
この前までは アザゼルに
さんざん 顔を赤らめてたのに｡
It wasn't that long ago that she was
blushing from Azazel.
The heart is a fickle thing.
心は移ろうものですクワァら｡
クワッ クワッ クワッ
クワッ クワッ クワッ！
Rage of Bahamut
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ･回想)((必ず 三種族が
共に生きる道があるはずです｡➡
There has to be a path where
all three races can live in peace!
私は それを諦めない！))
And I will never give up on it!
ありがとう！
(ﾊﾟﾝ屋)おっ ニーナ！
-Thanks!
-Oh, Nina!
あっ｡
戦勝記念のパンを焼いたから➡
I baked some bread for the celebration!
Why don't you take a loaf?
持っていきな｡
いいの？
Really?
今日のは
切れっ端じゃないぞ～｡➡
And these aren't your usual leftovers.
This is hot and fresh!
焼きたてだ｡
やった～！
Yay, thanks a lot!
ありがとうです～｡
(ﾊﾟﾝ屋)にひっ｡
ふふふふっ｡ あっ あら？ あっ…｡
(奴隷使いﾎﾞｽ)待ちな！
あっ｡
Stop right there.
はぁ～ また あんたなの？ 何よ？
You again? What do you want?
I promised didn't I?
I'm here to make you my slave.
約束どおり お嬢ちゃんを
俺の奴隷にしてやろうと思ってな｡
ドクン ドクン ドクン…(鼓動)
(手下)この… おらっ！
うわっ！
あっ 私のお肉！
あっ ちょっ… ああっ！
No! My meat!
ドカッ！
うっ！
ぐっ！
どうした？
What's wrong? Can't do anything
when you're on your own?
１人じゃ何もできねぇか？
Stop it!
≫(市民)やめてやれよ！
≫(市民)まだ子供だろ！
She's still just a child!
(心の声)≪もう嫌 この体！≫
I hate my body so much!
(手下)なんだ？ 貴様｡
あっ｡
Who the hell do you think you are?
あ痛たたたっ！ うわっ！
(手下)てめぇ… うわっ！
(奴隷使いﾎﾞｽ)ぐっ！ おととっ…｡
-Damn you!
-Whoa, whoa, whoa.
そりゃ！ うわっ ぐわっ！
Take this!
あ… あれは…｡
(手下)うっ ぐっ！
That's...
お… おい 行くぞ｡
Come on, let's go.
≫コツ コツ(足音)
≪やばい…≫
Oh, God. This is bad.
This is bad. This is so bad.
≪やばい やばい やばい やばい≫
腕力だけでなく 足も速いのだな｡
Not only are you strong,
but you're fast as well.
Why did you not fight back?
なぜ 彼らに抵抗しなかった？
That's...
それは
私 女の子だから…｡
Because I'm a girl...
なぜ 顔を上げない？
Why are you looking down?
ニーナだったな｡
えっ！
Nina, was it?
You remembered.
覚えていてくれたんですね｡
私に何か用か？
はっ！
Did you need something from me?
あ… あの… 今夜➡
Tonight is the night before Anatae's
big festival, right?
アナティのお祭りの前夜祭でしょ｡
ああ｡
I'll be running a food stand with a friend.
仲間と屋台を出すんです｡
助けてもらったお礼がしたいので
来てくれませんか？
I want to thank you for helping me,
so would you come by?
この前 腕相撲した馬車が
目印です｡
You'll know it from the carriage
when we arm wrestled.
そうか 分かった｡
I see. Very well.
"I see. Very well," huh?
｢そうか 分かった｣… か｡
"I see. Very well."
｢そうか 分かった｡➡
そうか 分かった｣｡ へへへっ…｡
"I see. Very well."
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ？
(ﾘﾀ)ん？ 遅かったじゃない｡
What took you so long?
What happened to these peppers?
(ﾘﾀ)何よ このへたれた唐辛子！
(ﾊﾝｻ)お肉は？
Where's the meat?
落としちゃった｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)落とした!?
I dropped it.
You dropped it?
(ﾘﾀ)
落としたら拾えばいいじゃない｡
Then why didn't you just pick it up?
そうか…｡
(ﾘﾀ)ん？
Oh, right.
いや 踏んづけられちゃったの｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)誰に？
-It got stepped on!
-By who?
悪い人たち｡
えっ… 何よ それ｡
By bad people.
What?
ごめんなさい｡
まあいいわ｡
Sorry!
Whatever.
このへたれた唐辛子で
料理しましょう｡
I'll have to make do
with these sad peppers.
手羽先は ある分だけで…｡ ん？
I guess these
are all the wings we'll have.
Perhaps she's shocked
from dropping the chicken wings.
(ﾊﾝｻ)手羽先を落としちゃったのが
ショックなのでしょうクワァ？
I know what I told him,
but what if he really shows up?
≪あんなこと言っちゃったけど
ほんとに来たら どうしよう…≫
I'll turn into a dragon. I just know I will!
≪私 竜になっちゃう｡
絶対なっちゃう～！≫
来る｡ 来ない｡ 来る｡ 来ない｡
He'll come. He won't.
来る｡ 来ない｡
クワッ… 何してるんですクワァ！
やめてくださいよ！
What are you doing? Stop that please!
何してんですかって…｡
あははっ ははっ！
What am I doing?
ドサッ！
(ﾊﾝｻ)しどい…｡
This is terrible!
(側近)陛下！
ん？
Your Majesty!
Where have you been?
今まで どちらに お出ましに
なっておられたのですか？
You must tell one of us
when you decide to leave the palace.
お出ましのときは 必ず
おっしゃっていただきませんと｡
黙れ｡
Quiet.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)明日の正午
人間どものパレードが出発する｡➡
Tomorrow afternoon, the humans
will be putting on a parade.
パレードは
城の正門からスタートし➡
The parade will begin
from the castle gates,
城下の中央通りを進み➡
proceed down the center of the city,
make its way around the plaza,
広場で迂回して
城へと戻るルートだ｡➡
and return to the castle.
ポイントとなるのは
この場所だ｡➡
The crucial point will be here.
まずは パレードを
ここで止める必要がある｡➡
The parade will need to be
stopped here first.
I will use that as a signal to come down
from the north here with the red dragon.
俺は それを合図に
ここから 赤い竜と共に南下する｡
(ﾀﾞﾝﾃ)挟み撃ちか｡
A pincer attack?
The soldiers in black armor should prove
the most troublesome.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)最も厄介なのは
あの黒い鎧の連中だ｡➡
俺が
ヤツらを赤い竜に引き付ける｡➡
I will draw them to the red dragon.
残った兵と人間の王を➡
While I do, you will split up into two groups
ふた手に分かれた貴様らで
総攻撃を仕掛けるのだ｡➡
and attack the remaining troops
and their king.
第一部隊は
高台からの遠距離攻撃｡➡
The first squad will conduct a range attack
from high ground.
第二部隊は
接近戦により 確実に王を殺せ｡
The second squad will engage in
close combat and slay the king!
But this plan
relies heavily on the red dragon.
(ﾀﾞﾝﾃ)しかし
完全に 赤い竜頼みの作戦だな｡
All we can do is trust you.
There's no room for failure.
俺たちは
お前を ただ信じるしかない｡➡
失敗は許されんぞ｡
Who do you think you're talking to?
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)誰に言っている｡
Rage of Bahamut
パン パン パン パン！
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)
街は こんなに浮かれてるのに➡
The town's so festive...
なんか さえないっすね 俺たち｡➡
Apart from us, that is.
団長は
何も感じないんすかね この状況｡
How's that make you feel, Captain?
((お前は
お前の思うように生きてみよ))
You live your life your way.
((私は 私の正義を貫くだけだ))
I will be doing what I feel is right.
Dias, I am leaving you in charge!
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)ディアス ここは任せる！
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)はっ！
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)ま～た単独行動かよ…｡
There he goes off on his own again.
ダダダダ… ダン！
あっ｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)いらっしゃい いらっしゃい｡
ここの手羽先 おいしいよ｡➡
Welcome, welcome!
We have delicious wings!
でも 俺のが もっとうまいよ｡
食べさせないけどね！
But mine taste even better,
not that I'll let you eat me!
(ﾘﾀ)そんなに呼び込んだら
間に合わないわ｡
We'll run out if you draw that many in.
(ﾊﾝｻ)はい どうぞ｡
Come on in!
ニーナ ぼう～っとしないの｡
危ないでしょ｡
Nina, stop spacing out. It's dangerous.
は～い｡ ふふっ｡
Okay.
(ﾊﾝｻ)いらっしゃい いらっしゃい｡
唐辛子焼きは絶品だよ！
Welcome, welcome!
Our spicy wings are to die for!
Nina, are you okay?
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)
ニ… ニーナちゃん 大丈夫か？
Would you leave me alone please?
ほっといていただけませんか？
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)あっ…｡
Now, now! These wings are perfect
さあさあ
祭りの夜には ぴったりだ！
for a festive night like this!
They'll light a fire in your belly!
腹から燃えるよ｡ あっ
おにいさん お久しぶりですね｡
Oh, hey there, young man!
Good to see you again!
(ﾊﾝｻ)これが うわさの
腕相撲のイケメンですよ｡
This is the handsome guy
from the arm wrestling we mentioned.
ふ～ん なかなかね｡
He's not bad.
１つ 返し忘れた｡
えっ？
I forgot to return one to you.
あっ…｡
い… いらっしゃいませ～！
Welcome!
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)おい 若ぇの｡
なんだ？
Hey there, youngblood.
What?
ちょ… ちょっと バッカス
何してんのよ｡
What are you doing, Bacchus?
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)
うちの手羽先は うめぇんだが➡
Our wings are great,
スペシャルは これで終わりだ｡
but this is the last of our special.
いいのか？ 私がもらっても｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)ああ｡➡
Are you sure you want me to have it?
Of course!
そのかわりと言っちゃなんだが
この子と➡
But would you do me a favor
and take this girl
around to see the festival with you?
前夜祭を見て回ってくれねぇか？
えっ？
ガキのくせに
意外と胸は でけぇ…｡
She's got a big chest for her age.
ふんっ！
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)うぐっ！ どわ～っと！
バ～ッカじゃないの？
-You're so stupid.
-Very well.
分かった｡
えっ!?
Say what now?
な… なんだ？
これを食べたら行こう｡
We can go after I finish this.
ドクン ドクン ドクン…
パン パン パン パン！
(一同)おお～！
Would you like one?
食べるか？
あぁ～…｡
それは むいて食べるんだ｡
You are supposed to peel it first.
えっ｡ あっ… 知ってるわよ｡
I knew that! Of course I knew that.
知ってますとも｡
おいしい！
It's so good!
ほんとに大丈夫かしら？➡
Are you sure about this?
It doesn't matter how great he is.
いくら すてきっていったって➡
This is her first time
going out alone with a boy.
男の人と
二人っきりで出かけるなんて➡
初めてでしょ？
(ﾊﾝｻ)大人になって➡
She might come back all grown up!
帰って来るかもしれませんね｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)ぶぅ～～！➡
Hey!
おい！
(ﾘﾀ)あんたが唆したんでしょ？➡
You're the one who put them up to it!
ったく…｡ 祭りの最中に
竜にでもなったら大惨事よ｡
You'd better hope she doesn't turn into
a dragon in the middle of the festival.
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ…｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)うぅ…｡
やってみるか｡
えっ？
Would you like to try?
む… 無理だよ
私 こんな踊り知らないし｡
No way, I can't.
I don't know this dance at all.
How was I able to dance like that?
≪なんで
私 踊れちゃったんだろう≫
≪あんな近くで顔を見て
しかも 手まで握っちゃって≫
I got so close to him,
and we even held hands.
≪ああ～ 無理 無理 無理！≫
No, no, no!
I haven't danced like that
since I was a child.
踊ったのは子供のとき以来だ｡
えっ？
You were quite good.
なかなか うまかったじゃないか｡
うっ…｡
初めてには感じなかった｡
It did not feel like your first time.
そ… そんな｡
Really?
That was the first time
I've danced with a man,
私 男の人とダンスをしたのも➡
街を二人っきりで歩いたのも
初めてです｡
and the first time I've been out alone
in the city with one like this.
私もだ｡
うそ！
Me as well.
Yeah, right!
You were so good at dancing.
ダンス
あんなに上手だったじゃない｡
あっ｡
ダンスはできる｡
I know how to dance, but I have never
walked around the city with a lady before.
しかし
女性と街を歩いたことはなかった｡
It was fun.
楽しかった｡
うぐっ！
Could you tell me your name?
教えて あなたの名前｡
My name? My name is
名前か…｡ 名前は➡
Chris.
クリス｡
クリス…｡
Chris.
Will I see you again?
また会える？ また踊りたい｡
I want to dance with you again.
I don't know.
それは分からない｡
どうして？
Why not?
I hope we can see each other again.
また会えるといいな｡
えっ…｡
I hope we can see each other again.
(ｼｬﾘｵｽの声)会えるといいな｡
会えるといいな｡➡
会えるといいな｡
I hope we can see each other again.
ワン ワン！
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)ぐわっ！ ううっ…｡
痛ててっ…｡ あっ ごめんなさい！
I'm so sorry!
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)ちっ お前か｡
Oh, it's you.
Who are you?
誰？
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)俺だ｡
It's me.
アザゼル！ どこ行ってたのよ？
Azazel! Where have you been?
ムガロちゃんのことを
置いてきぼりにして｡
How could you leave Mugaro like that?
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)時が来た｡
えっ？ 何？ なんの時？
The time has come.
What? What time?
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)明日 パレードが始まったら
あの塔の下に来い｡➡
When the parade begins tomorrow,
go to that tower there.
それじゃない｡ こっち｡
Not that one, this one.
あっ… ごめん｡
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)必ず来い｡
Sorry.
Promise me you'll be there.
What was with his attitude?
何よ 威張っちゃって｡
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)ちっ｡ また お前か｡
You again.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)こんな所で何をしている？
What are you doing here?
Preparing for the festival.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)祭りの準備さ｡
何をするつもりだ？
What are you planning on doing?
ふふふっ｡ 楽しみにしてろ｡
You just wait.
貴様らの記念日を
俺たちも盛大に祝ってやる｡
We will be joining you
in your big day of celebration.
(ﾆｰﾅの声)｢お母さん 今日
私の中で 何かが はじけました｡➡
Dear Mom,
Something happened to me today.
こんな衝撃は
生まれて初めてです｡➡
I've never felt this way before.
もしかして｣…｡
Could it be?
パン パン パン パン！
これが 恋!?
Is this love?
It's okay, it's okay
I cast the usual spell
Stagnation, stagnation
My words and heart are at odds
Default
I've taken all the paint
And mixed up all the colors
Until you're left with me
So fragile
Yet strong
Close to overflowing
But not spilling
Because I'm incomplete
I won't amount to much
This is just a good luck charm
I'm not asking for your help
I was just clinging to you
Let's end it all today
I'm done living this pointless life
I've taken my last pointless breath
To whom it may concern
See ya and goodbye
I killed the person I was yesterday
To whom it may concern
See ya and goodbye
A new morning is coming
行くぞ｡
Let's go.
Charioce!
-Raggy!
-Raggy?
Wasn't it uncomfortable to be wrapped
up so tight?
-The rags stretch!
-Oh, right.
Next time on Rage of Bahamut:
Virgin Soul, "The Day of Victory."
Raggy! Oh, never mind.
Baha Soul!!
Baha Baha Baha Soul!
I demand you watch
the next episode.
Don't you dare disappoint me.